So it's not up to you to drop this
You're just being emotional
Come back with me
We'll settle this privately
Every time we settle it privately
My feelings always get brushed aside
Don't embarrass yourself
Dignity isn't given by others
You maintain it yourself
If you really leave with him today
Don't come crawling back to me
Gu Chengze
I won't be the one to regret this
Do you really think he can protect you
Protection takes more than just words
You will see
Don't you regret this Su Mingyao
Save those words for yourself
Me mentioning the Civil Affairs Bureau
Wasn't just to scare Gu Chengze
Are you sure
I'm sure so are you going Mr Fu
I am
If you just want to
get rid of Gu Chengze
I can help you this far